Contacts

Date of birth 06.12.1989

City Vilnius

Phone +370 602 902 14

E-mail egle.ct@gmail.com

About me

I am a beginner web developer who is looking forward to new challenges in programming and automation area. Before I developed an interest for coding, I was an experienced IT Service Desk support analyst at *Danske Bank Group IT Lithuania* for over 2 years. In order to re-establish myself as a developer, I have completed intensive programming courses for beginners at Vilnius Coding School and then PHP courses at Code Academy. To better understand IT infrastructure, I have obtained knowledge and certificate of ITIL, in addition, I had an opportunity to cover a Queue Manager role in Application Integration team within Danske Bank for 3 months. To sum up, I have a keen interest in computer science, knowledge about IT infrastructure, great communication skills, I understand the value of good service objectives and I am excited for new opportunities within IT world.

Education

01.09.2009 - 30.06.2013

English Philology and German Language (Bachelor degree) at Šiauliai University

01.04 - 30.07 / 2012

English Philology and German Language University of Hildesheim

Trainings

20.12.2017 - 26.01.2018

PHP courses at Code Academy

26.10 - 13.12 / 2016

Programming courses for beginners (introduction to C#, Java, JS, HTML, CSS and MySQL) at Vilnius Coding School

07-09.11.2016

Windows 10 Client: New Features and Upgrade (Danske Bank)

16-18.08.2016

ITIL Foundation (Danske Bank)

01.10 - 01.11 / 2014

Evening language program (German) at University of Westminster, London, UK

Skills

HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP

JS, JQUERY

PHP, MYSQL

WORDPRESS, GITHUB

Languages	Speaking	Understanding	Writing
English	Perfect	Perfect	Perfect
German	Average	Average	Average

Native **Lithuanian**

Work experience

since 01.02.2018

Freelance Web Developer at www.visuallab.lt

18.05.2015 - 01.09.2017

IT Service Desk support analyst at Danske Bank Group IT Lithuania DGITL

01.03 - 01.06 / 2017 Temporary positioned as Queue Manager in Application Integration team within Danske Bank.

13.01.2014 - 01.03.2015

Lounge catering staff at Institute of Directors, London, UK.